Jonathan Carter

123 Second Street, Omaha, NE 34567 j.carter@youremail.com (123) 456-7890

Self-motivated and independent accounts receivable clerk with close to two years of experience maintaining payment tracking across all company departments. Skilled at bookkeeping procedures and financial reconciliations. Able to increase operational efficiency and profitability by providing timely and accurate billing.

Key Skills

- Highly analytical with expert math skills
- Accounting Software: Xero and Quickbooks
- Microsoft Office Suite: Word,
 Excel, and Access
- Ability to work independently and on a team
- Works efficiently and calmly under pressure
- Accurate and fast at data entry

Professional Experience

Accounts Receivable Clerk

Electrical Designs Limited, Omaha, NE I July 2019 - Present

- Maintains accounts receivable documentation, including bank reconciliations and financial reports
- Enters and codes all invoices efficiently and accurately to accounts waiting for payments
- Provides backups to the Accounts Payable Manager to process bi-weekly checks for accounts payable
- · Researches and resolves accounts payable discrepancies
- Creates new customer accounts and enters data into the central database

Part-time Administrative Assistant

Robert Morris, Omaha, NE j September 2018 - July 2019

- Worked with the company accountant to manage bank accounts and process payroll
- Assisted with gathering tax information fpr external audits
- Provided administrative support to the accounting department
- · Called customers for debt collection

Education

Associate in Applied Science in Accounting

Metropolitan Community College, Omaha, NE, September 2017 - June 2019

Certifications

- Accounts Receivable Manager Certification (ARM), Institute of AR Finance and Management, 2020
- ♦ Microsoft Office Specialist (MOS) in Excel, 2018